Fighter. Lover. Brother. Father.
I Am Ali is a documentary film directed by Clare Lewins.
Unprecedented access to Muhammad Ali's personal archive of "audio journals" as well as interviews and
testimonials from his inner circle of family and friends are used to tell the legend's life story.
Self (archive footage), played by Muhammad Ali.
Self, played by Jim Brown.
Self, played by George Foreman.
Self, played by Tom Jones.
Self, played by Mike Tyson.
Self, played by Muhammad Ali Jnr.
I Am Ali is a 2014 documentary directed by Clare Lewins.
It covers the life of professional boxer  Muhammad Ali.
The film tells his story using personal audio
recordings Ali made himself during the 1970s.
Additionally, interviews of friends, family members, and people associated with professional
boxing, combined with archival footage of Ali, are used throughout the movie.
Notable appearances in the film include George
Foreman, Jim Brown, and Mike Tyson.
The film explores themes of sports, wrestling,
biography, sports documentary, woman director.